Guide to the University Historical Material records, 1821-2012 RG0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Images and visual works, 1859-1990; RG0031 Series 1; 21 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 34, Flat box 37, Box 42, Box 86, Box 95, Box 205, Box 206, Box 265, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269, Box 270, Box 271, Box 87, Flat box 89, Flat box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Box
  - Joan Donaldson, candidate for homecoming queen, 10/1949 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Text on photograph: [label] "For Release Sunday, October 23, 1949 Miss Joan Donaldson, 20, daughter of Mr. C.W. Donaldson, 900 19th St. NW is The George Washington University Homecoming Queen candidate of Tau Kappa Epsilon fraternity. The student selected will be crowned on Oct. 29 during the Homecoming Ball to be held at National Guard Armory. Other event[sic] include a debate with Oxford U. On Oct 27 a football game with Lafayette College on Oct. 28, and on Oct. 29 a luncheon honoring 10 members of the faculty who have served 25 years, a tour of the new Student Union and a reception." Formerly photograph #PB-264
  - Dr. Edward Condon, 1960 ca. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Text on photograph: "Dr. Edward U. Condon, director of the National Bureau of Standards" Formerly photograph #PB-265
  - John F. Dulles with President Eisenhower at Walter Reed, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Text on photograph: "John Foster Dulles and President Dwight D. Eisenhower at Walter Reed Hospital, 1959. U.S. Army Photographer, Walter Reed" [and] "Dulles LLB [1926 crossed out] 1912, Eisenhower DPS 1964 (This is an honorary degree)" Formerly photograph #270
  - President Eisenhower with John Dulles at Walter Reed, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Text on photograph: "President Dwight D. Eisenhower visits Secretary of State John Foster Dulles at Walter Reed Hospital. 1959"
  - President Eisenhower with Vice President Nixon and John Dulles, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Text on photograph: "President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Vice President Richard Nixon, and Under Secretary of State Clifford Herter visit Secretary of State John Foster Dulles, at Walter Reed Hospital. 1959 JFD d. 5-24-59/resigned 4-15-59" Formerly photograph #PB-272
  - Progressive resistance table at University Hospital, 03/18/1948 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Text on photograph: "Marjorie Ionta [below "2223 H St. NW"] (on table) and Chief Physical Therapist Dorathy voss demonstrate "progressive resistance "table at the new George Wash. University Hospital. 3-18-48" Formerly photograph #PB-274
  - Physical medicine department, 05/1948 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Text on photograph: "Physical Resistance Table, May-1948, Chief Physical Therapist Dorathy Voss, Dr. E. Leong Way." [and] "FWA-48-94 May, 1948 Chief Physical Therapist Dorothy Voss treats Dr. Edward L. Way, patient, on the physical resistance table in the Physical Medicine Department of the New George Washington University Hospital, Washington, 7, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-275
  - Maternity room at University Hospital, 08/1950 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Text on photograph: "Washington, D.C., Neg. No. 48-79-A FWA, Mothers occupying double rooms in the maternity ward of the George Washington University Hospital in Wash. D.C. may elect to be placed in rooms which face view windows overlooking the nursery for four where their babies are cared for - two double rooms face into the nursery. Federal Works Agency Photo" Formerly photograph #PB-164
  - Pathology lab with Dr. Robert Hill, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Text on photograph: "Dr. Robert Pelley Hill does research in the Pathology Laboratory at The George Washington University Hospital. (1952) Dr. Hill is associate professor of pathology at The George Washington University School of Medicine." Formerly photograph #PB-276
  - X-ray facility with Sarah Paxton and Larry Dempsey, 04/1948 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Text on photograph: "Sarah Paxton, x-ray technician, and Larry Dempsey, (dark room technician posing as patient) using a 500 milliampere x-ray at the New George Washington University Hospital in Washington, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-277
  - X-ray facility with Sarah Paxton and Larry Dempsey, 04/1948 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Text on photograph: "FWA-48-105 April 1948 Sarah Paxton, X-Ray technician, and Larry Dempsey, (dark room technician posing as patient) using a 500 milliampere X-Ray at the New George Washington University Hospital in Washington, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-278
  - Virginia Stillman and Edna Martinson with x-ray machine, 03/20/1948 ca. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Text on photograph: "Virginia Stillman, left, and Edna Martinson, nurses adjust the 500 milliampers x-ray equipment at the new George Washington University Hospital in Washington, D.C. March 1948 W. Post Photo 3-20-48 * now Mrs. Eva [Bertraun?]" Formerly photograph #PB-279
  - Henry Crecy Yarrow, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Text on photograph: [signed] "H.C. Yarrow" Formerly photograph #PB-285
  - George W. Samson bust, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Formerly photograph #PB-160
  - Carver Barracks on Columbian College grounds, 05/27/1862 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    The negative for this image is housed in box 0258, barcode 32882017673214. Formerly photograph #PB-259, negative NA-78.
  - Frank Wigglesworth Clarke, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Text on photograph: "Frank Wigglesworth Clarke 1847 - 1931" Formerly photograph #PB-286 Professor of Chemistry
  - Charles E. Munroe,"Prof of Chemistry, Chief Explosives Chemist US Bureau of Mine, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Text on photograph: [signature on front] "Charles E. Munroe" [and] "Return to B.D. Van Evira The George Washington Univ. Washington, DC." Formerly photograph #PB-288 Professor of Chemistry, Chief Explosives Chemist, US Bureau of Mine
  - Edwin Allston Hill, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Formerly photograph #PB-289 Professor of Chemistry
  - Hiram Colver McNeil, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Formerly photograph #PB-290 Professor of Chemistry
  - Baby and mother moved from H Street hospital to new University Hospital, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Text on photograph: "This young mother was one of the patients removed from the old George Washington University Hospital at 1335 H Street nw. to the big new hospital on Washington Circle. Her baby, in an incubator, made the trip in the same ambulance. 4-1-48" Formerly photograph #PB-291
  - Law School building, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Formerly photograph #PB-294 Law School Building, 1865-1884
  - Lisner Library rear exterior, 1940 ca. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Text on photograph: "Rear view of Lisner Library 2023 G St., nw" Formerly photograph #PB-299
  - Lisner Library rear view, 1940 ca. (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Text on photograph: "Rear view, Lisner Library 2023 G St., nw" Formerly photograph #PB-300
  - Front view of Lisner Library and adjoining buildings, 1940 ca. (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Text on photograph: "Front view of the library, showing the adjoining buildings" Formerly photograph #PB-301
  - Jacob Burns Law Library, exterior from 20th Street, 1969 ca. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Text on photograph: "Jacob Burns Law Library 20th St. N.W., between G and H Sts." Formerly photograph #PB-303
  - Reserve room at Lisner Library, 1968 ca. (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Text on photograph: "Lisner Library" Formerly photograph #PB-302
  - Jacob Burns Law Library and Stockton Hall, 1969 ca. (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Text on photograph: "Stockton Hall and Jacob Burns Library #63 20th St., between G and H Sts." Formerly photograph #PB-304
  - Law School Building, 1921 ca. (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Text on photograph: "The Law School The George Washington University when located at 1435 K st nw" Formerly photograph #PB-305 The negative for this image is housed in box 0258, barcode 32882017673214. Formerly negative, NA-88.
  - Law School Building at time of purchase, 1920 ca. (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Text on photograph: "The George Washington University Law School, 1435 K. St. Wash. D.C. 1920-25" Formerly photograph #PB-306
  - Law School Building 1425 K Street, 1922 ca. (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Text on photograph: "This building formerly stood at 1435 K Street, NW and house the Law School of The George Washington University from 1920 to 1925." Formerly photograph #PB-307
  - Masonic Temple, Law School, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Text on photograph: "Masonic Temple 801 13th N.W. Law School in the 5th and 6th floors fron [sic] the fall of 1910 to the summer of 1920. The George Washington University, Washington, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-308
  - Mrs. Alice Sorrell, 100,000th patient, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Text on photograph: "Mrs. Alice Sorrell, the 100,000th patient to be admitted to George Washington University Hospital, was among those transferred from the old institution on H Street to the big new teaching hospital on Washington Circle. April 1, 1948" [and] "Nurse is Miss Edith Billheimer RN - graduate of GW School of Nursing 1925 2100 Eye St nw" Formerly photograph #PB-310
  - Dr. Clarence Hartman/Moving nursery patients to new GWU Hospital on Washington Cirlce, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Text on photograph: "First ride in an incubator. This baby was transferred from the old George Washington University Hospital on H Street, Washington D.C., to the big new hospital on Washington Circle, in the ambulance with her mother. April 1, 1948." [and] "Dr. Clarence R. Hartman in civilian dress (head of out Patient Dept)" Formerly photograph #PB-311
  - Patients transferred in ambulance to University Hospital, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    Text on photograph: "Patients transferred from the old hospital on H Street, nw., are received at George Washington[,] Washington's great new teaching hospital on Washington Circle, Washington, D.C. Army ambulances were used." [and] "April 1, 1948" Formerly photograph #PB-312
  - Optical shop in University Hospital, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Text on photograph: " FWA 48-96 1948 George R. Smith, manager of the optical shop in the Eye Department of the New George Washington University Hospital, in Washington, D.C. edging a lens."
  - Optical shop in University Hospital, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    Text on photograph: "1948 George Smith, manager of the optical shop, demonstrates the new cylinder surfacing unit (used to finish the surface of astigmatism correcting glass to Mary Everist Kramer, head of the Orthoptic section of the Eye Dept. of The George Washington Univ. Hospital, Wash., D.C." [and] "Star Staff Photo Eye Department" Formerly photograph #PB-314
  - Eye Department in University Hospital, 03/25/1948 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Text on photograph: "Eye Department March 25 - 1948" [and] "April 1948 Washington, D.C. Dr. Williams Errgong, resident in the Eye Department, examines Mary Everist Kramer, supervisor of the orthoptic department. The binocular ophthalmoscope gives a microscopic picture of the eye in three dimensions. The New George Washington University Hospital." [and] " Slit lamp - instrument to examine the interior of the [eye] microscopically. (Shown with doctor & patient). Binocular ophthalmoscope - instrument to examine the interior of the eye microscopically and with third dimension. Cabinet with trail lenses for the testing of refractive errors. On top of cabinet is shown a model of a brain with the nerve connections of the eye - made by Dr. Wm. Errgong. Ophthalmic chair with complete refracting unit. Lensometer - to check glasses for correct grinding of prescription. Lens exhibit of colored lenses. Campimeter - instrument to map out blind spots of the visual system and tracing blood vessel shadows." Formerly photograph #PB-315
  - Edwin Allston Hill, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Formerly photograph #PB-316 Professor of Chemistry
  - Charles E. Munroe, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
    Text on print: [front, autograph] "Charles E. Munroe" Formerly print #PB-287 Professor of Chemistry at George Washington, Chief Explosives Chemist, US Bureau of Mines.
  - Charles Riborg Mann, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Text on photograph: "Charles R. Mann, Trustee of G.W.U." Formerly photograph #PB-317
  - Newell Ellison at Cherry Tree Planting Ceremony, 02/22/1965 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    Text on photograph: "The George Washington University Washington, D.C. 20006 February 22, 1965 Board Chairman Newell W. Ellison turns a spade of earth at the Cherry Tree Planting Ceremony." Formerly photograph #PB-318
  - Miss Minnie Rock, first patient transferred to University Hospital, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    Text on photograph: "The first patient to be transferred to the new George Washington University Hospital, on Washington Circle, from the old hospital building on H Street, nw., Washington, D.C. Patients were moved in Army ambulances. Miss Minnie Rock April 1, 1948" [and] "Nurse is Miss Edith Bill [Heimer?], graduate of the g.w. School of Nursing 1925 2100 Eye St. nw" Formerly photograph #PB-319
  - Transfer of patients from H Street to University Hospital, 04/01/1948 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Text on photograph: "April 1, 1948 Fifty patients were removed on March 31 from the old George Washington University Hospital building on H Street, nw., Washington, D.C., to the big new multi-storied teaching hospital on Washington Circle." Formerly photograph #PB-320
  - Biochemistry class at the Medical School, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
    Text on photograph: "Biochemistry" Formerly photograph #PB-321
  - Cloyd H. Marvin, Philip Fleming, Walter Bloedorn at ceremony, 03/23/1948 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    Text on photograph: "Dr. Cloyd Heck Marvin, president of the George Washington University, conferring the honorary degree of Doctor of Civil Laws on Maj. Gen. Philip B. Fleming, Federal Works Admistrator [sic] and the honorary degree of Doctor of Science on Dr. Walter A. Bloedorn, medical director of the George Washington University Hospital on Tuesday, March 23, 1948. Washington, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-322 The Washington Post March 24, 1948 pg.11 "GWU Takes Formal Possession of 5-Million-Dollar Hospital"
  - Cloyd H. Marvin and Philip Fleming at ceremony, 03/23/1948 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    Text on photograph: "Dr. Cloyd H. Marvin (left) presents the Doctor of Civil Laws degree to Maj. Gen. Philip B. Fleming, administrator of Federal Works Agency. Presentation was made during opening ceremonies of The George Wash. U. Hospital" Formerly photograph #PB-323
  - Major General Philip Fleming receiving honorary doctorate, 03/23/1948 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    Text on photograph: "Maj. Gen. Philip B. Fleming, Federal Works Administrator, Receives congratulations upon receiving the honorary Doctor of Civil Laws Degree at the Convocation formally opening the George Washington University Hospital, March 23, 1948. Formerly photograph #PB-324
  - Biochemistry laboratory in Medical School, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    Text on photograph: "Biochemistry - Medical School" Formerly photograph #PB-325
  - Medical School laboratory, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
    Formerly photograph #PB-326
  - School of Medicine and old University Hospital, 1946 ca. (Box 4, Folder 73)
    Text on photograph: "The School of Medicine at 1335 H Street nw. (right) and the old University Hospital at 1337 H Street nw." Formerly photograph #PB-327
  - Warwick Memorial building, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    Text on photograph: "1950 Warwick Memorial building houses The George Washington University Cancer Clinic. Housed the George Washington University Hospital 1898 - 1948." Formerly photograph #PB-328
  - Medical School, 01/1950 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    Text on photograph: "Medical School of The George Washington Univ. Jan. 1950" Formerly photograph #PB-329
  - Officers of Brooklyn Alumni Club, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    Text on photograph: "Officers of Brooklyn Alumni Club G.W.U. 1947" [and] "Spiegler '26, Gromet '34, Rogers '28, Richman '23, Fradkin '27" Formerly photograph #PB-334
  - Abram Lisner, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 77, Box 280, Folder 2)
    Text on photograph: "Mr. Lisner" Formerly photograph #PB-339. There is also a larger version of the image with #PC-36.
  - Cloyd Marvin presents honorary degree to Syngman Rhee, 07/30/1954 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    Text on photograph: "Dr. Cloyd H. Marvin, President of the George Washington University, congratulates President of Korea Syngman Rhee. The occasion was the Special Convocation of the University to award Dr. Rhee the honorary degree of Doctor of Laws. Dr. Rhee was graduated from the George WAshington University in 1907. The Special Convocation was held 7-30-54 at the University's Lisner Auditorium in Washington, D.C." Formerly photograph #PB-341
  - President Elliott with student at awards tea, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    Text on photograph: "Pres. Elliott (left) with Robert Alan Blanar, who received a math award at awards tea, 1967" Formerly photograph #PB-342
  - Communications laboratory in Tompkins Hall, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    Text on photograph: "Tompkins Hall of Engineering -- Communications Laboratory 1956" Formerly photograph #PB-357
  - George A. Betts, Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
    Formerly photograph #PB-360 Brother of Dorathy Marvin
  - Dorothy Betts Marvin, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    Formerly photograph #PB-361. This image also includes George Betts.
  - Rupert Woodward, University Librarian, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    Formerly photograph #PB-362
  - Ralph Remley, honorary memember of Friends of Libraries, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    Formerly photograph #PB-363
  - Kennedy C. Watkins at Friends of Libraries Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    Formerly photograph #PB-364
  - John R. Mason, Mr and Mrs. Kennedy Watkins at Friends of Libraries annual meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    Formerly photograph #PB-365
  - John Mason and Thomas Manson at Friends of Libraries' Annual Meeting., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    Formerly photograph #PB-366
  - John Boswell at Friends of Libraries Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    Formerly photograph #PB-367 Please note: see item RG0031-001-0004-00098 for a different image of this same event. This other image has some different data about this event.
  - Kennedy Watkins at Friends of Libraries Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    Formerly photograph #PB-368
  - Kennedy Watkins at Friends of Libraries Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    Formerly photograph #PB-369
  - Art students at Corcoran Gallery, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
    Formerly photograph #PB-371
  - Drafting classroom in Tompkins Hall, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    Text on photograph: "Tompkins Hall of Engineering ** Drafting Classroom 1956" Formerly photograph #PB-372 The negative for this image is housed in box 0258, barcode 32882017673214.
  - Power laboratory in Tompkins Hall, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    Text on photograph: "Tompkins Hall of Engineering -- Power Laboratory 1956" Formerly photograph #PB-373
  - Industrial processes testing, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    Text on photograph: "Tompkins Hall of Engineering _ _ View from instructor's office to floor of Industrial Processess Testing Laboratory. Fall, 1956." Formerly photograph #PB-374
  - Heat-power laboratory in Tompkins Hall, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    Text on photograph: "Tompkins Hall of Engineering _ _ Heat - Power Laboratory 1956" Formerly photograph #PB-375
  - Professor William J. Turner introducing speaker, 04/27/1975 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    Formerly photograph #PB-376
  - Prize winners in student book collection contest, 04/27/1975 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    Formerly photograph #PB-377
  - Third prize winner in student book collection contest, 04/27/1975 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    Formerly photograph #PB-378. Text with image "Third prize winner in student book collection contest congratulated by John F. Boswell." Please note: see item RG0031-001-0004-00088 for a different image of this same event. This other image has some different data about this event.
  - John Russell Mason, University Librarian, undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
    Formerly photograph #PB-379
  - Intramural tennis champions, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    Formerly photograph #PB-385
  - First design of Lisner Auditorium, 1942 ca. (Box 4, Folder 101)
    Text on photograph: "First design for Lisner Auditorium" Formerly photograph #PB-386
  - Friends of the Libraries annual meeting with Mary L. Robbins and Professor William Turner, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    Formerly photograph #388
  - Kathy Chiang, Margaret Clark. Linda Meyer and Alcione Amost at Friends of Libraries Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    Formerly photograph #PB-389
  - Professor Robert H. Walker, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    Formerly photograph #PB-390
  - 2nd prize winner Bruce Benesh in student book collection contest, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    Formerly photograph #PB-391
  - Joseph L. Metivier, Edith Phillips, and M. Lynch at Friends of Libraries annual meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    Formerly photograph #PB-392
  - William Matheson, Nina Matheson and Isabella Young, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    Formerly photograph #PB-393
  - Physics laboratory at Corcoran Hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
    Text on photograph: "Physics Lab - Corcoran Hall (2d floor)" Formerly photograph #PB-395
  - Lisner Library reading room, undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
    Text on photograph: "Lisner Library 1st Floor Reading Room" Formerly photograph #PB-396
  - Chemisty research laboratory, 03/1948 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    Text on photograph: "Photo chemical apparatus used in the study of the kinetics of the photo chemical isomerization of cis- and trans- dichlorethy- lenes sensitized by iodine. Research Lab. The George Washington University, March 1948. Work is being done by Richard Wallis, graduate student in chemistry (lower) under the supervision of Dr. Reuben E. Wood, Asst. Prof. of Chemistry (Standing)." Formerly photograph #PB-397
  - Botany students at work in laboratory, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    Formerly photograph #PB-398
  - Organic research laboratory students studying, undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
    Text on photograph: "Experimental Fractional Distillation Organic Research Laboratory" Formerly photograph #PB-399
  - Students viewing gastro-intestinal systems, undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
    Text on photograph: "Biochemistry" Formerly photograph #PB-400
  - Class of 1899 collage, 1899 ca. (Box 4, Folder 114)
    Text on photograph: "Class of '99 [1899]" Formerly photograph #PB-402
  - Prize winning entry in Student Book Collectors Contest, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    Formerly photograph #PB-404
  - William D. Johnson and wife at Friends of Libraries meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    Formerly photograph #PB-405
  - Elbert Staughton Wade, 1919 ca. (Box 4, Folder 117)
    Formerly photograph #PB-406
  - Lisner Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
    Formerly photograph #PB-407
  - Architect's conception of Lisner Hall, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    Formerly photograph #PB-409
  - Cooperative store, 06/1950 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    Text on photograph: "Cooperative Store, June 1950" Formerly photograph #PB-411
  - Snack bar on second floor of Student Union, 01/1962 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    Text on photograph: "Student Union 2d floor snack bar January 1962" Formerly photograph #PB-412
  - Cafeteria on 1st floor of Student Union, 01/1960 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    Text on photograph: "Student Union 1st floor cafeteria January 1962" Formerly photograph #PB-414
  - Lisner Library, main reading room, 04/1950 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    Text on photograph: "Library, main reading room showing the Gilbert Stuart Portrait of George Washington, in the University Library, The George Washington University. April 1950." [and] "Holmes I. Mettee Studio, Photography, 701 N. Eutaw Street, Baltimore 1 Md. No. 15239 D" Formerly photograph #PB-415
  - Periodicals reading room, Lisner Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
    Formerly photograph #PB-416